[
    {
      "question": "我____一杯咖啡。",
      "answer": "需要",
      "options": ["需要", "了解", "重要", "努力"]
    },
    {
      "question": "我还没有____去哪儿。",
      "answer": "决定",
      "options": ["决定", "影响", "需要", "了解"]
    },
    {
      "question": "这个问题很____。",
      "answer": "重要",
      "options": ["重要", "了解", "努力", "情况"]
    },
    {
      "question": "只要____，就会有收获。",
      "answer": "努力",
      "options": ["努力", "决定", "需要", "情况"]
    },
    {
      "question": "我____你的想法。",
      "answer": "了解",
      "options": ["了解", "需要", "决定", "重要"]
    },
    {
      "question": "你能告诉我一下____吗？",
      "answer": "情况",
      "options": ["情况", "影响", "决定", "努力"]
    },
    {
      "question": "天气会____我们的计划。",
      "answer": "影响",
      "options": ["影响", "了解", "需要", "我"]
    },
    {
      "question": "我不想错过这个____。",
      "answer": "机会",
      "options": ["是", "机会", "请", "再见"]
    },
    {
      "question": "他终于___了！",
      "answer": "成功",
      "options": ["支持", "了解", "成功", "需要"]
    },
    {
      "question": "我们需要____这个问题。",
      "answer": "解决",
      "options": ["适合", "解决", "努力", "重要"]
    }
  ]
  